这里是911,请表明身份
911. Please identify yourself.
有个男人在我家
There's a man in my house.
家里还有个宝宝,他要杀我们
I have a baby. He's going to kill us.
女士,谁在你家?女士,别挂电话
Who's in the house, ma'am? Ma'am, stay with me.
求求你,快一点
Please, hurry!
天啊,他要进来了
God, he's coming!
他要进来了
He's coming.
鲍威尔街有一位母亲和她的宝宝有被杀害的危险
Possible homicide in progress. Mother and infant.
在附近的小组请赶往处理.女士,请不要挂掉电话
Dispatch all vehicles in the area. Ma'am, stay with me.
不!不…
No! No!
你为什么要这样对待我？
Why are you doing this?
你是个坏母亲
You're a bad mother.
摇啊摇,摇到树梢
"Rock-a-bye baby, in the treetop
待风起,摇篮摇啊摇
"When the wind blows, the cradle will rock
树枝一折断,摇篮即落地
"When the bough breaks the cradle will fall
宝贝、摇篮和所有一切都将归于尘土
"And down will come baby
"Cradle and all"
孩子,让我结束这场恶梦吧
Let me finish your nightmare, kid.
你们情况如何？SWAT来了吗？
What's your status? Is SWAT here yet?
把这个地方看好
Secure your perimeter.
你们还在等什么？ 等SWAT小组
-What are you waiting for? -SWAT team.
他们会待上整晚的,看着楼梯
They'll be all night. Take the stairs.
电梯这里发现有烟
We've got smoke in here.
是他
It's him.
导演：林岭东
上
Go!
拜托,不要开枪
Don't shoot, please!
有看到陌生人吗 没有
-Is anybody else in there? -No!
克里斯,快下楼看看
Get them downstairs! Go!
去,快点 去看看
-Get them out! -Check it!
杰克,我们该等消防队来 当然,混蛋
-We've got to wait for the fire trucks. -Absolutely. Shit!
去把窗户打开,快去
Get those windows open. Go on!
快,动作快点
Come on! Move it!
孩子,来吧
Come on, baby!
走!
Go!
孩子,来吧
Come on, baby.
我没事,快离开这里
I'm okay. Get out of here!
等一下,你在干什么
What in hell are you doing?
没事了
It's okay.
快把孩子送去医院,确定是否没事
Take the baby. Get him to the hospital. Make sure he's okay.
嫌犯是男性白种人,正由豪瑟街往北走去
Suspect is a white male, heading north on Hauser on foot...
穿黑色毛外套
...wearing a black leather coat.
停车
Hold it there!
巴士快停车,把门打开
Stop the bus! Open up!
怎么了？ 各位,对不起
-What's going on? -Sorry, folks.
只是例行检查而已,没什么大不了
Just a routine check. Nothing to be alarmed about.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
抱歉,打扰各位了
Sorry for the inconvenience.
大家都站起来,面向窗户,别看我
Everybody up! Against the window. Don't look at me!
不要动
Freeze!
杰克,害怕了吧
Be afraid, Jake.
很害怕吧
Be very afraid.
我差点就抓到他了,真的
Almost had him. I had him!
是啊,现在他不是你的问题了
Well, that's not your problem anymore.
你在一个小时前就退休了
As of an hour ago, you're officially retired.
我知道
I know.
一旦找到车子,查血迹会查个水落石出
When they find the car they should check for blood.
闭嘴好吗,这不再是你的案子了
Shut up, okay. lt's not your case anymore.
我曾办过这个案子,我很关心能否破案
I popped him one. Check for blood.
你就是不肯罢手,对吧？
You just couldn't leave quietly, huh?
霍尔,我不需要你来帮我发表光荣的退休演说
You know, I wanted one last inspiring lecture from you.
十年来你全听他们的
Ten years, you've heard them all.
你还是对我那么凶.但在你离开前,联邦政府人员在现场,他们想跟你谈谈
A lot of good it's done. But, before you go, the feds are here. They want to talk.
跟我谈？ 他们当然想谈罗
To me? Of course, they do.
你好
Gentlemen.
杰克,我是唐莱兹曼.你好吗？ 我很好,你们想干嘛？
-Stan Reisman. How are you? -Fine. What do you want?
我知道你要退休了 没错
-I understand you're leaving the force. -That's right.
我们想提供你一份工作 不,谢了,我不需要
-We'd like to offer you a job. -No, thanks. Don't need one.
我们能帮你抓到他.他会再度行凶的
We can help you catch him. He will kill again.
昨晚有第十一名受害者遇害
Last night, the Torch claimed his 11th victim.
这位恐怖的连续杀人犯
This elusive serial killer has remained at large...
已经横行三年
...for over three years, preying on mothers...
专门威胁西雅图地区的母亲
...throughout the Seattle area.
杰克莱利警探曾经侦办过本案,应该挺身出来说明本案
Detective Jake Riley who has headed up the case had this to say about the Torch.
为什么凶手要折磨受害者？
How's it to be leaving with the Torch case unsolved?
我不予置评
No comment.
杰克,他打电话给你了吗？ 不予置评
-Has he called you? -No comment.
你是因为这位聪明的杀人犯而退休？
Is this brilliant killer the reason you're quitting?
我因个人因素申请退休 本案无可奉告
I'm retiring for personal reasons. It's got nothing to do with it.
杰克,少来了 好吧,我告诉你们一件事
-Come on. Give us something. -I'll give you something.
事实证明,喜欢杀人的大混蛋只是一个讨厌妈妈的小鬼
Our big bad bogeyman is nothing more than a bed-wetting mama's boy.
没错,他就是这样的人
That's right. He pisses himself all the time.
他是个变态的精神病患者.这样够了吧
Pathetic really. Just a sick pervert. Is that enough for you?
你们都录下来了吗？ 录下来了吗？
-Did you get that? -Did we get that?
你们都录下来了吗？
Did you get that?
亲爱的杰克,你的电话 谢谢您
-Darling, telephone for you. -Oh, thanks, Mom.
喂
Yeah?
杰克,你昨晚在电视上提到我的事可不是玩笑话
That was a nasty thing you said about me on TV.
是吗？你太敏感了
Oh, yeah? You're just a little too sensitive.
你给听我着,别再打电话给我,我已经退休了
I don't want you calling me anymore. I'm retired.
你可以退休,但你永远抓不到我
You can quit, but you'll never get rid of me.
我太聪明了
I'm too smart.
是啊,你妈会以你这个疯子为荣
Yeah, Mommy must be proud of her little psycho.
杰克,别说了,看看你自己
Stop it. Look at yourself.
你花了三年时间想抓我却徒劳无功,你是个坏警察
Three years trying to catch me. But you failed. You're a bad cop.
你以为你退休就能阻止我吗？
Do you think quitting would stop me?
我会继续杀人的
I'm going to keep on killing, asshole.
你是个真正的失败者 去你的,你这个婊子养的混蛋
-You're a real loser. -Fuck you, you fucking prick!
我会像疯狗一样去追捕你
I'm gonna track you down like a fucking dog!
你心知肚明,你这婊子养的
You understand, you son of a bitch?
去你的
Fuck you!
杰克,我也去你的
Fuck you, too, Jake.
受害者的背景几乎都一样
It's always the same M.O. with slight variations.
全是单亲母亲,都是被烧死的
Single mother. Mole. Burns them postmortem.
我们采集到部份指纹,甚至凶手的轮廓跟血型
We've got partial prints. Trace evidence. Blood type, even.
-But still no Torch. 但还是毫无头绪 -No shit. 不会吧
-But still no Torch. -No shit.
说点我不知道的吧
Tell me something I don't know.
我们将杀人凶手的资料
We fed enormous amounts of data on the Torch...
输入到超级电脑里,发现凶手是白种男性
...into our ViCAP supercomputer. We've come up with a white male.
三十多岁,非常健壮
Thirties. Very physical.
站在屏幕前
Step up to the mark.
杰克莱利,欢迎您
Welcome, Jacob Riley.
一年前的玛特西凶杀案里
The Martucci slayings, a year ago.
我们找到一根他的毛发,用来复制DNA足足有余
We found a hair follicle belonging to him. It was enough for a DNA imprint.
拉近看看
Take a closer look.
好吧,这是凶手复制人 一点都没错
-Okay. So this is a clone of the killer? -A replicant.
上帝花了六天创造出人类,我们则花更长时间做出复制人
God created man in six days. We took longer.
FBI从什么时候开始… 我们不是FBI
-Since when is the FBl- -We're not FBl.
我们是国安局的人
We're National Security Force.
我们不在乎什么连续杀人犯
We really don't care about your serial killer.
基本上此事牵涉到国家安全,恐怖份子才是我们的目标
Originally, this was developed for national security. Counter-terrorism.
当今情报系统无法找出这些恐怖份子
Today's intelligence has failed to weed out terrorists.
好吧,我懂了
Okay. Go on.
我们要创造复制人,帮我们找到元凶
Our goal is to create replicants that can lead us to them.
我懂了
I understand.
但他不是恐怖份子
He's not a terrorist, though.
对,但行为模式很相似
No. But the behaviour patterns are similar.
那么,为什么找我？
So, why me?
因为他挑上了你
Because he picked you.
你说他挑上了我是什么意思？
What do you mean he picked me?
当他准备好后会交给你看管,你负责照顾他
When he's ready you'll take custody. You'll care for him.
帮助开发他的潜能,再看看能否帮你找到凶手
Help him develop. Then you'll see if he can lead you to the killer.
让他的照片上电视来解决此事不是更容易？
Wouldn't it be easier just to plaster his face on TV?
不,这是机密计划,没有照片,不能使用传统办案技巧
This project is classified. No pictures. No conventional techniques.
你唯一的工具便是复制人
All you have is Replicant.
发生了什么事？
What's going on?
心脏出现逆反应,排斥荷尔蒙成长
A counter-reaction. He's rejecting the latest growth hormone.
快跟我说,有什么解决办法？ 不跳动了
-Talk to me. What can we do? -V-fib! Flatline!
把他放出来,快!
Get him out. Now!
欢迎光临我的世界
Welcome to my world.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
一号复制人,早上好
Good morning, Number One.
该起床了
Time to wake up.
我们今天要上基本课程,学习如何坐...
Today, we're going to cover the basics: How to sit...
立、走、停
...stand, walk and stop.
我现在在走路
Now I'm walking.
我坐了下来
I'm sitting.
我站起来
I'm standing.
我是强纳森女士,您好
I'm Miss Johnson. How are you?
跌伤了吗？
Did you hurt yourself?
你的小金童可能没有那么聪明
Maybe your golden boy's retarded.
物理读数正常,但脑波很低
Physical readings are normal, but the brain sign waves are low.
我们已透过基因重新排序加强他的精神感应能力
We've enhanced his telepathic ability through genome resequencing.
他可能是我们第一个用基因工程做出来的复制人
He may be our first, but genetic memory has been scientifically proven.
他只是需要人类的刺激
He just needs human stimuli.
那是厕所
That's the toilet.
那就是你来此的目的,和他展开人类的第一次接接触
That's where you come in: first human contact.
做得好,看着录影带再做一次
Good try. Watch the video and try again.
真是惊人,是不是? 他的学习能力超乎想像
-Impressive, isn't he? -He's exceeding expectations.
你们感到很高兴,对吧？
You guys are pretty happy with yourselves, aren't you?
你们不知道他有什么潜能
You have no idea what you're getting into there.
我想他第一件会做的事,是去杀11个女人
I've seen what he's able to do firsthand to 11 women.
如果事实证明他跟凶手一样,我们会很遗憾
If this thing turns out to be anything like the original, we're gonna regret it.
还好,一旦用毕,就可以处理掉复制人
At the end of the day, Replicant is disposable.
别紧张
Take it easy.
这是食物
Food.
吃吧
Eat!
我是杰克
I'm Jake.
你喜欢吗？觉得如何？
You like that? How about this?
觉得如何？
How's that?
嘿,这里
Here, here.
好,这里,看那里
Okay. Here. Look at that.
你喜欢吗？
You like that?
你很强壮嘛,放轻松
Strong, huh? Easy! Take it easy!
别紧张
Take it easy!
退后,退后
Back up! Back!
轻松,退后
Easy! Back!
现在坐下
Now, sit!
坐下
Sit!
我站起来了
I'm standing.
我在走路
I'm walking.
我坐下来
I'm sitting.
我站起来了
Standing.
我在走路
I'm walking.
我坐下来
I'm sitting.
我站起来 别动
-I'm standing. -Stay!
不对,走路
No. Walk.
来吧,我们走
Move. Let's go.
把太阳眼镜给我
Give me your glasses.
值五百块,小心点 是啊
-Those are $500 sunglasses. -Yeah?
看吧
Look.
谢谢
Thank you.
我该怎么处理这家伙？拿到他的使用手册？
Do I get an owner's manual on this guy, or what?
你只能等他心中的杀机出现
You do whatever it takes to awaken the killer inside.
这是国安局临时工作证明,还有你的枪
Here are your temporary NSF papers. And your gun.
知道了 你每十二小时要向我报告一次
-Got it. -I want a report every 12 hours.
好,我们走吧
Okay. Let's go. Walk!
坐下
Sit.
杀人犯的睡觉模样真是可爱
Sleeping killer. How sweet.
是啊,我们有同伴了
We've got company.
好了,科学怪人
Okay, freak-of-science.
我们就从这里开始谈起,你想到什么了?
Let's talk a little shop here, shall we? What do you remember?
你想到什么了,快点
What do you remember? Come on.
你这个杀人犯,你想杀人吗？
Are you a killer? You feel like killing?
除了女人,喜欢杀任何人？让我看看你是怎么做的
Killing somebody other than a woman? Show me how you did it.
让我看看你是怎么做的，来呀
Show me how you did it, come on.
让我看看你是他妈怎么做的
Show me how you fucking did it.
记得这个吗？
Remember that?
拿去
Take it.
拿好
Here.
你想杀我吗？机会来了
Want to kill me? Here's your chance.
Do it.
动手吧
把枪放下，把枪放下！
Drop the gun! Drop the gun!
三位大狗熊来救我了
Three stooges to the rescue.
保持冷静,不要射到目标。杰克,叫他退后
Stay calm. Do not shoot the subject. Jake, tell him to back off!
不,开枪杀了他
Just shoot him. Kill him.
杰克你真该死 好了,兄弟们,放轻松
-Goddamn it, Jake. -Okay, boys. Take it easy.
你们把枪放下，他可能也会那么做的
Maybe if you put your guns down, he'll do the same.
很好
That's good.
如果你再做出妨碍计划的事,我们会把他带回去
You deliberately jeopardised a classified project. We're taking him back.
太好了
Good riddance.
他一点用处都没有
He's useless.
非常好 你弄断了我的胳膊！
-Very nice. -You broke my arm!
让他们看看你的厉害
You shouldn't have showed him the moves!
No!
受伤了？
Hurts, don't it?
不要动 不
-Freeze! -No!
你知道这是百万计划 不是告诉过你不能杀他吗？
Million-dollar project! No shooting, remember?
把枪拿开
Put it away!
That's it. Put it away!
不要动
Stay! No!
别动
Stay!
Here.
坐
Sit.
别动
Stay.
很好
Good.
我会替你叫计程车. 走路
I'll call you a cab. Walk.
走路
Walk.
Yeah, hi.
嗨,我想要跟您约个时间去看伯克雷的房子
I'd like an appointment to see the house on Berkeley.
我叫杰克莱利 把枪放下
-My name is Jake Riley. -Drop the gun!
闭嘴
Shut up!
对不起
Excuse me?
抱歉,是收音机里的声音
Sorry. It was the radio.
半小时,太棒了,谢谢
Half hour. Great. Thank you.
你知道这个地方吗？
You know this place?
一年前这房子因你而声名大噪
A year ago, you made it the most famous house in the country.
真是一团糟
Real messy.
快点,退后,冷静一点
Come on! Get back! Calm the fuck down.
听到没有,冷静一点
You hear me? Calm the fuck down.
好了,走吧
Okay. Let's go.
只是下雨而已,来吧
It's just rain. Come on.
今天天气如何？您是杰克莱利吗？
How about this weather? Jake Riley?
我是温蒂卫尔康
Wendy Wyckham.
冷静一点
Calm the fuck down.
No.
抱歉,我的表弟兰利有点特别
Sorry. My cousin Ron is a little special.
我带你们进去 乖一点
-Let me show you in. -Be good! Come on.
这栋房子建于1926年
This house was built in 1926.
所有的木工都是原来的模样
All the woodwork is original.
一进门就看到温暖的小火炉,感觉很特别
A nice cosy fireplace here makes the entrance that much more special.
这里是一间大起居室
Over here, we have a spacious living room.
这边请
This way.
我们现在看到的是厨房,才刚翻修过
Here, we go into the kitchen which has recently been remodelled.
所有的大理石都是法国货
All the marble, of course, imported from Florence.
这里是餐厅,很适合款待宾客
And over here, we have the dining room. It's perfect for entertaining.
您说您是从事哪一行的？
What line of work did you say you were in?
我是干警察的
I was in law enforcement.
没错,你是电视上的那位警察 你在侦办一起凶杀案
That's right. You're that TV cop. The Torch case.
真的是太好了
I feel so much better.
你知道这座房子的历史吗？ 我知道
-You know the history of the house? -Yes, I do.
真是太可异了,许多人都无法摆脱过去的阴影
You know, it's such a shame because most people can never get past it.
But it is a steal.
但这栋房子真的是物超所值
Way below market value.
他没事吧？ 你能让我们独处一下吗？
-Is he okay? -Could you give us a minute, please?
当然可以
Absolutely.
走吧
Let's go.
走路
Walk.
走吧，快
Let's go.
你想起什么来了？
What do you remember?
什么？你想到了什么？
What? What is it? What do you see?
他以前来过这里吗？ 是另外一个人来过
-Has he been here before? -In another life.
走吧
Let's go.
我不想回家,我想去公园
I don't want to go home. I want to go to the park! Now!
强尼,住口,你是个坏孩子
Johnny, stop it! You're a bad boy.
孩子，你还好吧？
-How you doing, kiddo? -Good.
跳上来，来吧
Come on! Jump up!
跳上来
Up you go!
你是个好孩子吗？
How you doing? You've been a good boy?
跳上来
Up you go!
一切都还好吧？ 很好,妈妈在做你最喜欢吃的菜
-How's things going? -Good! Mommy's making your favourite.
真的是太好了
I like that.
去帮我抱抱你妈妈，快去
Go give Mommy a hug for me. Go!
要乖一点
Be good.
丹尼，到楼上去好吗,让小康陪你去？
Danny, go on upstairs, okay? And take Scout with you.
好吗? 小康，来吧
-Okay? -Scout, come!
来吧
Come on.
坐下
Sit. Down.
你想告诉我这是怎么回事？
You want to tell me what the hell is going on?
这是机密。如果我告诉你，就得杀了你
Classified. If I told you I'd have to kill you.
事情非同小可
That's not funny.
抱歉，我知道.听着,我需要你的帮助
Sorry, I know. Listen, I need your help.
我需尽快找地方安置这家伙
I've got to get a rendering of this guy as soon as possible.
我不会帮你这个忙的
I'm not going to do that for you.
我得遵守规定，没忘记吧？
That's against department policy. Remember?
所以我才会来求你帮忙
That's why it's considered a favour.
喔，好恶心，那不能吃!
That's gross! Don't eat that!
那是给狗吃的,拿去,吃吃看
That's for doggies. Here. Try this.
还要吗？
Want some more?
你该说谢谢的
You're supposed to say, "Thank you."
怎么了？
What happened?
宝贝，发生什么事了？
Baby, what happened?
到这来，起来！
Come here. Get up!
你这混蛋,你对他做了什么？
You son of a bitch! What did you do to him?
小康咬我的舌头
Scout hit me in the tooth.
小康？等一下，杰克
It was Scout? Wait a second.
杰克，住手，不是他干的
Stop! It wasn't him.
小康咬伤他的舌头,是狗干的，不是他干的
Scout knocked his tooth out. It was the dog. It wasn't him.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
我踢了他几脚，一场误会而已
I kicked the shit out of him. Honest mistake.
杰克,已过了18个钟头.你带他逃跑，要他攻击我的人
It's been 18 hours. You've gone AWOL, let him attack my men...
现在你还告诉我虐待我的复制人?
...and now you're telling me you've mistreated my replicant?
或许是我判断错误 或许你说得对
-Perhaps I made an error in judgment. -Perhaps you did.
或许你该把你的实验品带走.我才不需要你的混蛋
Perhaps you should take your experiment and go. I don't need your shit.
杀人犯和你说话后打算如何？我以为你想逮住他
After what the Torch said to you, I thought you'd really want to nail him.
你怎么知道他是怎么说我的？
How do you know what he said to me?
你窃听我的电话，是吗？
You got my place wired, is that it?
你怎么知道我们今天在哪里？
How did you know where we were today?
你也在追踪我们？
You tracking us, too?
你想我们会在不了解你的状况下
You think we'd let you out with the future of our national security...
把国家安全机密交给你吗？
...without knowing everything about you?
每隔12小时你要向我报告一次
I expect a report every 12 hours.
不准有例外状况
No exceptions.
杰克，是你吗？ 对啊，妈，是我
-Is that you? -Yeah, it's me, Mom.
把衣服脱掉
Get your clothes off.
对，好，不要动
That's it. Good. Stay!
一定不在车内，那太明显了
Not in the car. Too obvious.
让我看看你的牙齿
Let's see.
在嘴里，对吗？张大一点
Internal, is that it? Open.
内置追踪器,他们自以为聪明
Internal tracking device. They think they're real smart.
放在嘴里，真聪明不是吗？
Internal. Smart, isn't it?
没事，冷静
It's okay. Calm down.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
妈，我在工作
I'm working, Ma.
没事，事情不是像你想像那样
It's okay. It's not what you think.
妈，我们出去
Let's go, Ma.
杰克
Jacob!
什么事？ 那个人被打得满身是伤
-What? -That man was beaten up.
妈，你根本不认识他
Ma, you don't even know the guy, okay.
杰克，等一下，我说的是你
Wait a minute! I'm talking about you.
你到底是怎么了?发生了什么事？
What is the matter with you? What has happened?
你是怎么了?你为什么要那样子对他?
-What's wrong with you? -Why are you treating people like that?
妈，拜托别说了
Mom, stop. Please.
好吧，但是你给我记住一件事
Okay. But remember one thing:
如果你把别人当成罪犯看待,他们早晚会变成罪犯的
If you treat people like criminals, that is exactly what they will become.
你的晚餐在冰箱里,我回家了
Your dinner's in the fridge. I'm going home.
谢谢
Thank you.
我无法忍耐了
I can't take it!
你毁了我的一生
You have ruined my life.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
Bad boy! 坏孩子
Bad boy!
你得接受惩罚
You must be punished!
你是个坏母亲
You're a bad mother.
嘿，你没事吧？
Hey, you all right?
放开她
Leave her alone!
别激动，兄弟
Easy, man.
谢谢帮忙，我欠你一次
Thanks for the favour. I owe you one now.
算了吧
Forget about it.
看这里,不要动
Right here. Stay.
Subject loaded.
好，我们来看看你还记得什么
Okay, let's see what you remember.
这个如何？
How about this one?
还记得那个吗？
Remember that one?
快跟我说
Come on, talk to me.
开始扫描照片了 快一点，好吗？
The picture's scanned. Make it snappy, all right?
坐下，快坐下
Sit down. Go on, sit.
爱德华沙佛德
"Edward Garrotte."
显赫人物，1995年由南非移入
Outstanding. "Immigrated from South Africa, 1995."
杰克? 警长，盘价情况还好吧？
-Jake? -Captain, how's the market?
石油价格下滑
Well, oil prices are down.
你回这里来做什么？
What the hell are you doing here?
我只是清掉一些档案,全部清完了
I was just cleaning up some files. All done now.
你在开我玩笑？ 不，我得走了
-Are you jerking me around? -No, got to go.
你在开我玩笑？
You're jerking me?
闭嘴
Shut up.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
待在这
Stay.
走吧
Let's go.
我的天啊
Jesus Christ.
下一位受害者
Next victim.
拿去
Keep it.
杰克，我们是非法侵入民房
Jake, we have an illegal entry.
真是丧心病狂
This is one sick puppy.
凶手,你抓到他了，
The Torch. You got him.
就坐在你车子里 不是这样，我稍后再解释
-That's him in the car. -No. I'll explain later.
杰克，我得通知总部
Jake, I've got to call this one in.
You...
退后!
...back off!
快出去，快闪开
Get out! Go!
快打电话求救
Call for help.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
他在哪里？他一定知道
Where is he? He knew.
杰克!这是怎么一回事？
Jake! What the hell's going on?
告诉我这是怎么一回事 现在不行，我把他弄丢了
-What's going on? -Not now! I'm gonna lose him.
他是凶手，就在你车子里
That's the Torch. You got the Torch in the car.
不，不是他,他只是个饵
No, it's not him. He's the key.
我得去找他 杰克，等一下
-I got to find him. -Jake, wait a minute!
你是什么人？
Who the fuck are you?
Break it up!
快住手
Back off.
你无法再打电话了
No more phone calls.
你是谁？你想做什么？
Who are you? What do you want?
你想做什么？
What do you want?
你这混蛋
You asshole!
我把他弄丢了.他的情况如何？
I lost him. How is he?
他的情况如何？
How is he?
你一直在跟我说谎
You've been lying to me.
马堤尼中庭发生一起枪击案
Gunfire reported at Martini's Lounge, 9th and Renfrew.
根据目击者描述,凶手是男性，穿黑色皮夹克.在附近地区的警员请回答
Caucasian male, black leather jacket. Any units in the area....
就在两个街口远的地方
That's two blocks away.
有两个男人在打架,他们射杀了我老板
There were two guys fighting and they shot my boss.
然后就离开了
Then they took off.
冷静点
Calm down.
两个家伙长得一模一样
Two guys. ldentical twins.
在打架 待在这里
-They were fighting. -Stay here!
警卫说有一对双胞胎在打架
The janitor said that it was two identical twins fighting.
一模一样的双胞胎
Identical twins.
往前开
Go. Straight.
Yeah?
我以你为荣，你还活着
I'm proud of you. You're alive.
他是谁？
Who is he?
你那么聪明不会自己想吗？
You're so smart, figure it out for yourself.
我会想到的
I will.
他将会是我最大的挑战
It will be my biggest challenge yet.
你想干什么？
Watch where you're going.
嘿,老兄,走开
Hey, buddy. Come on, beat it.
快走开,你快走开
Get out of here. Yeah, you. Get out of here.
杰克，我的复制人怎么样了？
Hello, Jake. How's my replicant?
很好，他乖乖上厕所
Fine. Shits and pisses in the toilet.
想赖床
Wants to get laid.
也还没杀任何人
Hasn't killed anybody yet, though.
你了解我的意思
You know what I mean.
没错
Yeah, I do.
对了
And, yeah...
发生了一件事,我认为他想起另一个本尊
...something's happening. I think he's remembering stuff.
太好了.有什么我们可帮忙的吗？
Excellent. What can we do to accelerate the process?
不必了
Nothing.
他靠自己就做得很好
He's doing fine just on his own.
但我采取了不一样的方法
But I've chosen a different approach.
是什么呢？
Yeah? What's that?
什么？我以为你知道呢
You don't know?
你不知道我们现在在哪里？
You don't know where we are right now?
你没在追踪我们？
Aren't you still tracking us?
拉萨提街4901号
4901 LaSalle.
杰克，那是红灯区
That's the red-light district.
没错
That's right.
嘿，宝贝，干嘛那么急？
Hey, baby, what's the hurry?
喜欢你看到的东西吗？
Like what you see?
嘿，我们去散个步吧
Let's take a walk.
来吧
Come on.
自己随意
Make yourself comfortable.
好了，接下来要做什么？
So, what's it gonna be?
坐下
Have a seat.
先把衣服脱掉吧
Let's just take this off.
我们脱吧
There we go.
好吧，我们可以那么做
Okay, we can do that.
好了,这是前戏.我要看到钱
Okay, that's all the freebies, baby. Now I've got to see the green.
好，就像我说过的,一百块,先付钱吧
Okay. Look, I said $100. Pay up.
一百块，先付钱吧
$100. Pay up.
你得先付我一百块，先付钱吧
I said $100. Pay up!
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
放开我,他妈的，放开我
Let me go! Get the fuck off of me!
放开我
Let me go! No!
对，我有大麻烦
Yeah, I got me a deadbeat.
你是怎么了？
What the hell is wrong with you?
你是处男吗？
Is this your first time?
天啊，混帐
Oh, shit.
我不知道会这样
Look, I had no idea.
就当做什么事都没发生，好吗？快走
Let's say it never happened, okay? Go!
快走吧
Come on. Go!
住手
Stop it.
快住手，走吧
Stop it! Go!
付款有问题吗？
We got a problem with payment?
我是来收钱的
I'm here to collect.
放他走，他不知道他在做什么
Leave him be. He doesn't know what he's doing.
闭嘴,你喜欢上这家伙?
Shut up! You like this guy or what?
你知道规矩的，不是吗？
You know the fucking rules, don't you?
不要再打我了
I've had enough.
住手，放了他,拜托!
Stop it! Leave him alone! Please!
警察，不要动
Police! Don't move!
快趴下，不要动 别开枪
-Get down! Freeze! -Don't shoot!
快趴下，趴下
Get down, now! Get down!
趴下
Get down!
兄弟，别激动
You men. Easy, boys.
杰克，发生什么事了？
-Come on, man! -What's going on, Jake?
没事，他跟我一起的，我会抓到他
It's okay. He's with me. I'll get him.
好了，别激动，放轻松，坐下
Okay. Take it easy. Relax. Sit down.
没事的，你会没事的 跟他去吧
He's all right. You'll be okay. Go with him.
我帮你把外套拿来了
I brought you your coat.
出来后要来找我喔
Look me up when you get out, okay?
快点
Come on.
你还记得这是什么吧？ 兄弟帮帮我，快想想
What is it you remember? Help me out, buddy. Think.
我想起来了
Remember.
很好
That's it.
坏孩子
Bad boy.
坏孩子？你是什么意思？
Bad boy? What do you mean "bad boy"?
哈罗，妈妈
Hello, Mama.
你想起那些妈妈了？ 他杀了那些妈妈
Remember the mothers? The killing of the mothers?
跟我说你想起什么了
Come on, talk to me. What do you remember?
我想起来了
Remember.
看这照片，知道这女人是谁？
Look at this picture. Do you know this woman?
你查到线索了吗？ 没有找到DMV或护照
-Get the rendering? -No DMV or passport.
她应该是观光客或其它身份 该死,她是下个受害者吗？
-She's got to be a tourist or something. -Shit. Is she next?
看看这张照片 她会是下一个受害者吗？
-Look at this picture. -Is she next?
她会是下一个吗？
Is she next?
摇啊摇，摇到树梢,待风起，摇篮摇啊摇
"Rock-a-bye baby, in the treetop When the wind blows, the cradle will rock
树枝一折断,摇篮即落地
"When the bough breaks the cradle will fall"
你看到什么了？
What do you see?
我杀人
Me kill.
杰克，我是谁？
Jake, who am I?
你是基因复制人
You are a genetic double.
基因复制人?
Genetic double.
是，我也不知道是什么玩意儿
I don't understand it either, buddy, but....
你的本尊是个杀人魔
Your other half, he's a killer.
不
No.
上车吧
Hop in.
你就坐这里
It's all yours.
感觉不错吧？
Feel good?
很好
Good.
冰淇淋
Ice cream.
拿去
There you go.
拿去，你得帮我一个忙
There you go. You got to do me a favour here.
我要你看这张照片
I want you to look at that.
你知道那女孩是谁吗？
You know that girl?
你在想什么？
What are you thinking?
拿去,不对
Here, no.
是这里.把它画出来,很好
Draw up here. That's good, up there.
我看不懂，这是房子？
I don't know. House?
是教堂？还是什么？
Church? What?
到底是什么？
Go ahead.
我知道了
I got it.
我知道
I know.
能告诉我她是否住在这里吗？
Can you tell me if she's staying here?
麻烦再说一次？
Excuse me?
她是饭店的客人吗？
Is she a guest in the hotel?
你是谁？是警察吗？你有证件吗？
Who are you? A police officer? You have lD?
不要管我是谁,这位女士有危险
It doesn't matter who I am. She's in danger.
先生,对不起,饭店规定不准透露客人消息
I'm very sorry, sir, but hotel regulations strictly forbid....
对不起
Excuse me.
先生，没有饭店员工陪同,你不能上楼
Sir, you're not permitted upstairs unless accompanied by hotel staff.
好，我了解
Okay, I understand that.
我去叫警卫来.快出去，快出去
I'm calling Security. Get out. Get out!
不要动
Stay!
混帐
Shit!
把门打开，快
Open the door. Come on!
快去打电话
Make your call!
1404号房间发生火灾了。重复，1404号房间发生火灾了
We have a fire, 1404. I repeat, we have a fire, 1404.
从这里，我们走
Here. Go!
接近他了吗？
Is he close?
接近了
Close.
你在做什么？快回来
What are you doing? Get back.
回来把门打开
Get over here and open the door!
快把门打开，该死
Open the door, damn you!
快把门打开,快把门打开!
Open the fucking door! Open the door!
快回来把门打开!
Get back here and open the door, now.
Get over here! 快回来
Get over here!
快停下，马上回来
Stop and get over here right now!
回来，你这混蛋！
Get back here, you asshole!
该死
Damn it!
你看到我的留言了
You received my message.
你是谁？
What are you?
基因复制人
Genetic double.
克隆人？
A clone?
真是太不可思议了，太棒了
Un-fucking-believable. Fantastic.
太美了
Beautiful.
我的复制品
My exact replica.
我们都一样
We are the same.
一样？
Same?
对，我的身体就是你的身体
Yeah. My body is your body.
我的心灵就是你的心灵
My mind is your mind.
我的生命就是你的生命
My life is your life.
但是,我的好兄弟,杰克是不能相信的
But, my brother, Jake cannot be trusted.
他想杀你
He's going to kill you.
我会保护你的，兄弟
I'll protect you, my brother.
兄弟
Brother.
你要去哪里
Where are you?
我们是一样的
We are identical.
别挡路 一样的
-Get out of the way! -Identical.
别挡路
Get out of the way!
走开
Move!
你把他放走了
You let him get away!
我们都一样
We are the same.
我应该把你们两个都杀了
I should have shot you both.
天啊，他是在骗你啊
Goddamn you! He's screwing with your mind!
杰克想杀我？
Will Jake kill me?
杰克想杀我？我们两个是一样的
Will Jake kill me? We are the same.
杰克想杀我？
Will Jake kill me?
我们两个是一样的 闭嘴
-We are the same. -Shut up!
杰克，你负责侦办这案子吗？ 不是
-Jake, are you on the case? -No!
你重回警界了？ 我退休了
-Are you back on the force? -I'm retired.
可以透露其它更好的消息吗？
Can you say something better than that?
是一个拒绝负责任的人
Look, this is an individual who refuses to take responsibility.
就我所知，他不负责任
As far as I know, he's not taking responsibility.
他是个该死的大混蛋，没什么
He's a fucking nutcase, that's all.
我一直在等你的电话
I've been waiting for your call.
我知道，威士忌还好喝吧？
I know. How's your whiskey?
很好喝
It's fine.
我的复制人还好吧？
How's my replicant?
他很好
He's good.
把电话接上扩音器
Put us on the speakerphone.
我为什么要那么做？
Why would I want to do that?
我们可以谈谈，就像家人一样.我要你们俩都能听到我说话
We can talk, like family. I want both of you to hear me.
好了，说吧
Go ahead and talk.
我要他知道我有多爱他
I want him to know how much I love him.
他对我来说意义重大
What it means to me to have him in this world.
太棒了
How nice.
病态的爱
Psycho love.
想知道下一位受害者是谁吗？
So, do you want to know who's my next victim?
去问我的兄弟吧
Ask my brother.
Jake.
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
杰克，我在等时机
In time, Jake.
等时机
In time.
给我一个理由,否则把你的脑袋轰掉
Give me a reason, I'll blow your fucking head off.
把手伸出来,把手伸出来
Give me your hand. Give me your hand.
沙佛德先生，你好 卡罗，你好
-Hello, Mr. Savard. -Hi, Carol.
我妈今天情况如何？ 她今天比较好
-How's Mama today? -Well, she's had better days.
或许看到你，她会高兴一点 我要给她一个惊喜
-Maybe you can cheer her up. -I've got a surprise for her.
太好了
Good.
这一个
And this one.
我把她给分尸了,慢慢地分尸
I cut her good. Very slow.
我真希望你当时也在现场
I wish you were there.
她一直求我
She was begging.
一直尖叫
Screaming.
坏孩子，你应该受到惩罚,坏孩子
Bad boy, you must be punished! Bad boy!
你知道原因吗？
But you know what?
我是为你才这么做的
I did it for you.
你是个坏孩子
You bad boy!
你应该受到惩罚
You must be punished!
No.
不再是了，你这个婊子
No more, you bitch.
不再是了
No more.
我真不该生下你
You should never have been born!
卢克沙佛德
Luc Savard.
杰克，我查到了,是卢克沙佛德
Jake, I got it. Luc Savard.
天啊，真是坏孩子,11岁开始行窃
Jesus, talk about a bad boy. Shoplifting at 11...
曾偷过车子、吸毒、纵火
...grand-theft auto, narcotics, arson.
1988年加入海军陆战队
He enlisted in the corps in '88.
据报告1991年6月死于敌军阵营
Reportedly killed behind enemy lines in June of '91.
但是一直没找到尸体
But the body was never recovered.
我追踪过他的母亲
And I tracked down his mother.
温德妮沙佛德,六年前中风后,
Gwendolyn Savard. She was committed to the Nepenthe Home...
就住在内彭斯疗养院
...six years ago, after a stroke.
杰克，你猜怎么了？
One other thing:
这个女人杀了她的丈夫
This woman killed her husband.
把小孩锁在柜子里后,再放火把房子烧掉
She locked the kid up in a closet and then set the house on fire.
卢克沙佛德能够活下来,是因为那天下雨
Luc Savard only lived because it rained that night.
沙佛德先生？
Mr. Savard?
我们昨晚试图打电话连络你
We tried to call you last night.
他昨晚来过这里？ 没错
-He was here last night? -Of course.
我很遗憾,你母亲...
I'm sorry, your mother....
昨晚突然心脏衰竭,我们尽力救治
She had a sudden cardiac arrest. We did everything we could.
可惜回天乏术
She was just too frail.
这是她的东西
Her things.
对不起
Excuse me.
可以看她的遗容吗？ 当然可以
-May we see the body? -Yes. Of course.
杰克，别激动
Take it easy, Jake.
你要她死吗？你要吗？
You want her to die? Do you?
把枪放下
Your gun, drop it.
Drop your gun.
很好
Good.
显然你不够聪明
You're not so smart.
你不会再看到我走进来
You never saw me coming.
杰克，一切都结束了
This is it, Jake.
你死定了
You're going to die.
杰克，怎么了？
So, what's the matter, Jake?
没想到我会回来吧？
No smart comeback?
记者不在场，真无趣
No reporters to joke with?
他不是你的家人
He's not your family.
他不在乎你
He doesn't care about you.
但我在乎你,所以我要你跟我一起
But I do. That's why I want you with me.
我有个想法
I have an idea.
你去杀了他
You're gonna kill him.
杀了他
Do it.
把他干掉
Finish him.
Yeah.
不
No.
那你就得跟他一起死
That's why you're going to die with him.
他们以为你就是我
And they'll think you are me.
卢克沙佛德，你是个坏孩子
You are a bad boy, Luc Savard.
你说什么？
What did you say?
卢克沙佛德，你是个坏孩子
You are a bad boy, Luc Savard.
你杀了妈妈
You killed Mama.
Yes.
是，那又怎么样？感觉不坏啊
That's right. And so what? It felt good.
你这个妓女
You bitch!
你会没事的
Okay. You're gonna be okay.
别动，我马上回来
Don't move. I'll be back.
你要做什么？
There he is!
他在哪里？ 他下去那边了
-Where is he? -He's down there.
我的天啊
Damn!
嘿，妈妈的好孩子
Not bad for a mama's boy?
现在可以称为一则新闻了吗？还是稍后呢？
Should I call the news now or later?
住手
Stop it.
如果你杀了我,也就毁了你自己
If you kill me, you kill yourself.
卢克沙佛德，保险锁没打开
The safety, Luc Savard.
为什么你能感应到我？
What makes you think you can take me?
我可以看穿你的心思
I can read your mind.
看着我，醒醒，复制人
Look at me. Come on, buddy.
看着我 杰克
-Look at me. -Jake.
我的家人都死了
My family's gone.
他不是你的家人
He's not your family.
现在我是你的家人了
I'm your family. I'm your family now.
杰克，我看见雨了
Jake, I see rain...
在我眼睛里
...in my eyes.
我看见雨了
I see rain.
开门
Open up!
把门打开
Open the door!
把该死的门打开!
Open the goddamn door!
唯一能辨认的是冰柜里的尸体
Well, the only ones who made it were the corpses in the fridge drawers.
我要一份完整的报告
I expect a full report.
丹尼，你或许名列第一,但我比你更棒
Danny, you may be in first but I'm better than you.
才不是呢
No.
不，我名列第一.但是谁最优秀呢？
No, I'm in first. Who's the best?
是我
Me!
你看到送信人了吗？ 没有
-Did you see the delivery-man? -No.
我们去拿信吧
Let's go get it.
他喜欢雨
He likes rain.
嗨 嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
我就知道你会回来
I knew you'd come back.
我们离开这里吧，走吧
Let's get out of here. Let's go.